Umako, hear me out!
Don't come any closer, you hear me?
These soaps are really growing on me.
They're so engrossing.
Now, run away with me and we can be together.
It makes me happy to hear you say that, but I'm sorry.
I just can't. It's just not possible.
I don't give a damn about the Count and his power.
All that should matter is how we feel for each other.
I really want to hold Master's hand.
I can't hear my heart, but
どうしたけ言うの?
胸のベルが鳴る
始まりはあの時だった
君が目の前に突然
現れたのは生まれる前から
決められてたんだね
きっとそうだよ
願いや野望や
空想が
知らないレベルへ
ドアを探して
羽ばたく旅と
未来を
触れる
I can't hear my heart, babe
止められないよ
天使が鳴らしてる
大好きの合図だよね
Can you hear my heart, babe
どうしたって言うの?
聞いたことがない
胸のベルが鳴る
これでもまだ
君は何も知らないけれど
Culture
The Age of Exploration
heralded the start of a new age of cultural trade
During this era, the Europeans became aware of countless other peoples and cultures
Of course, they viewed the inhabitants of the Americas as savages, but they were fascinated by the enormity of their culture and the wealth they possessed
If this sounds like a certain Angeloid who insists on referring to humans as bugs, you'd be correct
She may see us as insects, yet she is still drawn to us
Yes, I'm with you
You're referring to Nymph, aren't you?
Because that doesn't really sound like Icarus
Yes, Mikako
Fascinating, isn't it?
Hmm
That too, Pooch
You're in on this too
Hey, look, it's time for the cultural fair again
Am I supposed to know what that is?
It's something we do at the private high school in town
All the different classes and clubs set up booths
They put on plays and concerts, you know, stuff like that
Master, will you be taking part in the fair too?
No, it's a pain in my ass
Only way I would is if my class forced me to join
The way I see it, I'm not in any club, so why should I even bother?
I've been waiting for you, Tomoki
We have a plan in the New World Discovery Club
Look, we're currently recruiting skilled pilots
Screw you!
Don't say that
You should be honored to even be considered
Given how many members we have in the running
Now wait just a damn minute
When the hell did I ever join your club, huh?
Well, according to the student council registry
We have you down as a card-carrying member
Conspiracy!
Someone's out to get me, I swear!
Wow!
These poor depraved children
What a pathetic excuse for an event
Look, Yoshitsune
They put a banner up for the cultural fair
I'm surprised they could afford that
Let alone pay for the fair
Do they even know the meaning of the word, culture?
It's those face turds from the academy
They think highly of themselves
They're from Sarami Academy, the private school I mentioned
The only reason we team up with them to put on this fair
Is because our school is so small being out here in the sticks
They don't seem very friendly
Time to watch the sparks fly
My goodness, Sukino
Are you seeing this?
They're actually making flowers out of cardboard
It begs the question
Can these cave people demonstrate culture
When they've barely discovered how to make fire?
Stupid yuppies!
If you're so great
What the hell are you doing for the festival this year?
Let me guess
Something big and flashy
Well, we have something that works, yes
We will be performing the classics
That's the dumbest idea I've ever heard
Did you hear that, Zoharo?
You're gonna put on some lame-ass boring playas
If anybody would want to see that crap
Why not just play a tape of Shakespeare
While you're at it, you freaking rich idiots?
It wasn't referring to the theater
You are such a moron, Tomo
He was talking about doing classical music
The poor cretin's never heard of classical music
It almost makes me feel bad for him
Come on, everyone
We'd better be on our way
I'm afraid this lack of civility may infect us
Way to go, genius
That big mouth of yours
Just put an even bigger target on our backs
Damn
They just declared war, Zohara
Now we have to do something for the fair
Yeah, I saw that
Any bright ideas?
Well, we could
I got nothing
Attention, everyone
The Prez has arrived
As your class president
I cannot allow this injustice
To stand another moment
If they're going to attack us with music
Then we shall retaliate with music
What do you say?
Want to start a band?
A band?
Like with instruments?
How the hell is she getting a tambourine
To make a sound like that?
This is hopeless
There's no way all of us talentless hacks
Will figure it out
But
What other choice do we have?
Master's hand
All I want to do is hold it
But how?
I know
I'll try really hard to play this tambourine
And when he tells me how good I did
I'll grab it
Nymph, that was awesome
Uh-huh
You know, you were really talented
I had no idea
You had an aptitude for music, Nymph
Well, I'm good with machines
So maybe that's why
If we can somehow base the song
Off of whatever you're playing
It won't sound so much like we're winging it
Now we're cooking
Let's show those private school douchebags
A thing or two
I just want you to know
We'll all be depending on you, Nymph
To be perfectly honest
I'm not that interested in being in a band
But since I'm just killing time
I may as well help you out
Sweet, thank you
The students from Sarami Academy
Have decided to pick a fight with us
At the cultural fair this year
Therefore, by extension
They have picked a fight
With the Satsukatane family
Of course, we live
This means war
And that is how Mikiko started
Her very own PR firm
With special thanks to the Satsukatane family
Almost immediately
Sarami Hai's attendance to the fair
Began to skyrocket
In direct opposition
The academy's PTA board
Called for an emergency rally
To garner support for their side
By pooling their money
They created their own PR machine
We will win this fight
As both sides began to attack each other
It drew the attention of the public
Who then took to the streets
To protest for each cause
Come with the academy
We support you, Tamaki
The joint cultural fair's music contest
Split Sarami City into two warring factions
Leaving it hanging on the edge of chaos
Life was put on hold
While everybody focused on their respective teams
Is it just me
Or is this whole thing getting completely out of hand?
Yeah, I guess we better start practicing, huh?
Icarus, do it again
You're gonna have to do this live soon
You need more practice
I'm sorry, Master
I'll work harder at it
Hey, Icarus
Yes, Soharma?
Something wrong?
You seem blue
No matter what I try
I can't be of any help to Master
I wouldn't worry about that
Seriously
I'm on drums
And I barely know what I'm doing
I know, but
That was perfect, Nymph
Absolutely perfect
It wasn't even that hard
Okay, guys
Let's go again
From the top
Here's an idea, Icarus
Perhaps the tambourine
Isn't the best option for you
No
Maybe there's something better
You can do in the band
Want to give it a try?
All right
Whoa
How did
Come on, come on
Now that the fair's here
I need to have some fun
There's still a little time
Before the performance
Welcome, Master
How many in your party today?
Icarus
What the holy hell
Are you doing here?
Someone in our class
Said they needed my help
So I'm helping
Tomo
What a nice surprise
Welcome
Zahara
Come on, buddy
Are you gonna order or what?
I'll just
Have a juice
And how about you?
Just a coffee
She's amazing
Oh, gosh
Tomo, can you stick around
A little longer?
Because I'm about to go on break
We should take a walk
Or something
Okay?
Um, yeah
Sure thing
So, what are you having?
A little more, please
Huh?
Bend over a tad more
I'm so excited for today
Where do you guys think
We should start?
Tomoki, check it out
What?
There's a haunted house
We should go
Hey, wait
What are you up to?
Just my exhibit
I thought I'd take advantage
Of the crowds
By promoting the
New World Discovery Club
And, of course
The upcoming concert
I see
You want to go up
In the sky that much?
You know
It's not always
Rainbows and sunshine
Up there
I can imagine
It's written all over
Yours and Icarus' faces
I'm bored
Entertaining
Would it please you
If I sing a song, Master?
Or I have an even better idea
I could kill all the bugs for you
That would not please me
You worthless bitch
Perhaps I should be rid of you
No, wait
Don't do that, please
I'll do anything you ask
Anything
Correct me if I'm wrong
But you had a little bird, yes?
Yes, I do
Would you like to see it, Master?
I found her one day
After she flew right into the synapse
All by herself
With her gorgeous feathers
And adorable little wings
She's really taken to me
I think we'll be best
Rip them off
Are you refusing to obey
A direct order
From your own master?
No
It's just
Now that was amusing
I suppose I shall keep you alive
For a while longer
Thank you
Thank you, Master
You always know what's right
I'm so happy
I could make you laugh
Hey, Nymph
We got this for you
You did?
I promised I'd get you something
Remember I said if my booth turned a profit
I'd buy you anything you liked
And you like these
Oh, that's right
I saw
You had your eye on these earlier
Plus you've been kicking ass in the band
So I wanted to give you something
Thanks for being awesome
Thanks
Is that what I'm supposed to say
Or
Thank you, Master
Thank you so much
Humans are no more than bugs
Simple creatures who we crush underfoot
Even if he is nice to me
He's still beneath me
It's so good
Isn't it?
Way to go, Tomo
You made her cry
You little devil
So wicked
No, I
What?
What are you doing?
Look, Nymph
The sky here is so vast
What does that even mean?
What the heck, Tomo?
Did you do something to upset Nymph again?
Don't look at me
I didn't do anything
Why are you all looking at me?
It wasn't my fault
This candy apple is awful
What are you talking about?
You just said it was good
Oh, shut up
Now, now, everyone
If you could just calm down
After all, it's almost time
The joint cultural fair's music contest
will now begin on the main stage
Please make your way to your seats
if you haven't already
We now give you the full orchestra
from Cerami Academy
Please give them a round of applause
If they don't realize how poor and underprivileged they are after this
they never will
This is what true culture is all about
Man, that was really good
I don't know how we're going to top that
Oh, man
You know what this means
The Academy is going to make fun of us again
Hey, don't count us out yet
We have Tomoki's band this year
They're bound to be good
I bet Tomoki's going to hit a home run for us
Our next act is a performance by the members of the New World Discovery Club
Tomoki! Tomoki! Tomoki! Tomoki!
Thank you
Thank you very much
I can hear the voices
They're calling me
The stage is my life
And now the time has come to show you all
how to rock
This song
is called
My Tingliness
I perk up whenever you're near
And it feels so good
You perk up when you see me too
Like I knew you would
Is it something God gave us as part of his plan?
I know it's hard
But don't be afraid anymore
Baby, touch my tingling nails
With your gentle hands
Yeah!
Tomoki, you know damn well that's not the song we decided on
I know, I know, but it was totally worth it!
Wow, that was an easy win
Thanks so much for the comedy, ingrates
How fitting for these feeble peasants to play a novelty song
Unfortunately for them it has led to our victory
Now that they've seen what happens
Perhaps they should shut up like the good future laborers they are
Sorry about that
That was a little bonus
For the fans
I love you guys
What's this?
Can you believe the nerve of this guy?
Huh
Now it's time for the real song
Here you go
This one's called
I'm falling down
Falling down
Blue
The sky up above
I want a soul forever
With you, my love
You, my love
You are the one who can fly
I've fallen and I'm stranded here
It's because my
My wings are heavy from the shame of all the ways that I've hurt you
You
Don't run away
Don't leave me here to cry in vain
So give me a sign
I'll try and I'll try
I know I can fly
To be with you
Blue is the sky that hangs above
Clouds are like tears
I cry in my love
I'm gonna spread these broken wings
And soar back into your heart
Cause that's when
I'm falling all over again
Falling for you
Falling down
Sparkling down
mocking the song
Long live Rock!
Did you see the looks on the faces of those Academy dicks?
Yeah, it felt so good to see them squirm.
We couldn't have done it without you, Icarus.
I am uncertain of that.
But I could not have done it without you, all of you, helping me.
Well, you were great.
Sugatsu, so were you, dude.
And you, nymph.
And of course, Sohara and the press.
I gotta thank all of you guys.
But mostly thank me,
because if I hadn't done that other song,
the real song wouldn't have sounded so good.
Yeah, I don't think so.
Tomoki, I wanted to ask,
are you planning to attend the bonfire tonight?
Bonfire?
Yeah, it's really lame, actually.
You have to go as a couple and hold each other's hands the whole time.
But since I'm single and all, I...
I'll go with you!
Help me your day, Tomo!
But I...
I can't believe I'm saying this,
but you've become quite the stud.
I'm a what now?
Hey, Tomo.
Why don't you take Alpha to the bonfire?
How come?
Why do you think?
She tried harder than all of us combined.
Totally.
You should take her out for a nice evening as a reward.
Doesn't that sound like fun?
Hmm.
Hmm...
Oh
Where would it be?
How are you going to say hello?
I'm sorry I'm sorry
You want illnesses?
I'm sorry
You can tell
Oh
Woo!
飛んで飛んで 上の空
やだろう 僕の刺激する
Don't buy! Don't buy!
今に見てろよ
アイギリスの運動
Is it wrong for me to be this happy?
The very weapon Master despises so much, is me.
Next time, off we go to my bathhouse paradise.